onlygoodlife.co 2019-08-22

# OnlyGoodLife.com – Your source for valuable information | Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

You will be informed each time our Site asks for personal information regarding how we intend to use your information. We may also have access to and collect some other personal information and data that is required to enable you to access the Site and its functionalities (cf. your IP address). OnlyGoodLife.com may use such personal information to measure visitor usage and interest, and help us improve the content and functionality of our Site. Unless a user has opted out by modifying his/her preferences, upon registration, we may use any e-mail address that we are provided with to notify users of the existence of new contents in areas concerning which they have expressed an interest. You may request that we stop sending you such notices, at any time thereafter, by following the instructions mentioned in our e-mails. OnlyGoodLife.com uses personal information collected from cookies and IP addresses as described below.

Information which we do collect about our Site’s users is stored at our offices at 6200 boul. Taschereau, bureau 304, Brossard QC, Canada, J4W 3J8, and on servers hosted at national-net.com.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

OnlyGoodLife.com does not and will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies, except to provide products or services you have requested, with your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  1. From time to time, we may provide some of the personal information that we collected to trusted business partners that work on behalf of or with OnlyGoodLife.com under confidentiality agreements which cover our users’ personal information as well as guarantees that our partner provides the same level of protection to your information as our organization does. As the case may be, such business partners may use your personal information to help OnlyGoodLife.com communicate with you about our offers and those of our marketing partners. However, our business partners do not have any independent right to share or otherwise use your information;
  2. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of OnlyGoodLife.com’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law;
  3. We may finally transfer information about you if OnlyGoodLife.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, OnlyGoodLife.com will notify you before information about you are transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Cookies and IP addresses**

Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they can be used to identify a user’s computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, if you do this, you may not be able to take full advantage of our Site. For example, our Site uses cookies to make it easier for users to download graphics from the site. We may also use cookies to collect demographic and profile data for purposes of delivering content specific to your interests through the Site’s interface.

An IP address is used by your computer every time it connects to the Internet, which is why this number can be used by Web sites to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our Site, as part of demographic and profile data (known as “traffic data”), so that such data (such as the Web pages that you request through our Site) can be sent to you. We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site. OnlyGoodLife.com will not use your IP address to attempt to identify you personally, nor to build a profile concerning who you are and what you search through our Site, otherwise that to provide you with the services and subscriptions that you request through registration or use of the Site.

**Advertisers**

From time to time, we may use an outside advertising provider to display ads on our Site. Such ads may contain or use cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web Site, cookies received with banner ads, as the case may be, are collected and used by our advertising provider. Please be advised that aside from allowing advertising providers to place such ads on our Site, we do not control nor have access to the information contained in or generated from the cookies placed on your computer by our advertising providers.

**External Links**

By its very nature, our Site contains links to third-party Web sites. Please be aware that we cannot control and are not responsible for the information collection practices of third-party Web sites. We encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies of these Web sites before visiting them or providing any information to them.

**Confidentiality and Security**

Subject to the foregoing, we limit access to your personal information to employees of OnlyGoodLife.com who we reasonably believe need to come into contact with such information either in order to do their jobs or to allow us to provide requested products and services to you. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect and restrict access to personal information about the users of our Site.

**Contacting the Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the personal information practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please send an email to contact@vmn.net, or contact customer support by regular mail at Visicom Media Inc., 6200 boul. Taschereau, bureau 304, Brossard QC, Canada, J4W 3J8.
